Getting to the top means taking down the competition.
Honor Society is a comedy film directed by Oran Zegman.
Honor is an ambitious high school senior whose sole focus is getting into Harvard, assuming
she can first score the coveted recommendation from her guidance counselor, Mr.
Willing to do whatever it takes, Honor concocts a Machiavellian-like plan to take down her top three student
competitors, until things take a turn when she unexpectedly falls for her biggest competition, Michael.
Honor Rose, played by Angourie Rice.
Michael Dipnicky, played by Gaten Matarazzo.
Mr. Calvin, played by Christopher Mintz-Plasse.
Travis Biggins, played by Armani Jackson.
Kennedy Park, played by Amy Keum.
Gary, played by Ben Jackson Walker.
Honor Society is a 2022 American coming-of-age comedy film
directed by Oran Zegman, written by David A.
Goodman, and starring Angourie Rice, Gaten
Matarazzo, and Christopher Mintz-Plasse.
It was released on Paramount+ on July 29, 2022, to positive reviews from critics,
with praise for the performances of Rice, Matarazzo, and Mintz-Plasse.
The film explores themes of high school, scholarship,
harvard university, manipulation, nerd.
The tone is lighthearted.